https://www.stmarys-bromley.org.uk/about-us/privacy-notice/

St Marys Bromley
HomeSt. Mary's Post LockdownChristmas ServicesSt. Mary's WorshipComplineOffline WorshipChildrenPreparation for Advent - 22 NovemberNews from the ChoirSt. Mary's NewsletterThe Digest from Rochester DioceseStudy GroupAfter lockdownAbout usAlan (the vicar)Monthly musingsHow to find St. Mary'sOur faithWho's whoContact usWho we supportChristian AidThe Children's SocietyTeams and meetingsPCCBATS CommitteeCommunications TeamFamilies Ministry CommitteeFamily Services CommitteeFinance & General Purposes CommitteeHouse & Hall CommitteeMagazine CommitteeSafeguarding CommitteeSunday Clubs CommitteeMinistry Planning TeamPastoral TeamPrivacy NoticeJoin inSunday WorshipWeekday WorshipWorship for Children and Young PeopleTwinklesMessy ChurchAdultsHome GroupsBible Reading NotesMothers' UnionMusicChurch ChoirFestival ChoirOrganist and OrganCurrent newsGrace CafeChurch Collection Envelope SchemeConcerts at St. Mary'sMusic at St. Mary'sPew paperCalendarCommunityChurch House and HallBATSBeavers, Cubs and ScoutsBrownies, Guides and RangersRegular ActivitiesCareplusJusBLinksParish SchoolNeed help?BaptismWeddingsCriteriaMarriage PreparationWedding costsFuneralsFuneral costsPrayerNames on Pew PaperPrayer LinkPrayer RequestGlossaryAdventElectoral RollEpiphanyLentPastoral AssistantThe PCCThe PeaceParish magazineSafeguardingHall HireGivingSearch
About usAlan (the vicar)How to find St. Mary'sOur faithWho's whoContact usWho we supportTeams and meetingsPrivacy Notice
Home > About us
> Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Data Protection - Privacy Notices
St. Mary’s holds information about people only to do with the life of the church. We ask people to agree for their information to be held for these purposes and are grateful when this is given.
The details of these uses can be involved and to describe them St. Mary’s has prepared two privacy notices. These have been authorised by the PCC.
The first Privacy Notice is for people with particular roles in the life of the church and can be found here:
The second Privacy Notice is for people who do not have a particular role in the life of the church and can be found here:
These documents also provides contact information of the Data Controller if you have any questions.
Privacy Notice-Non Role HoldersPrivacy Notice-Role Holder
This church website is powered by Church Edit
